oh we're gonna start my story or it
begins in childhood I was born I was an
80s child more than two weeks into the
80s and that definitely flavored my
childhood because it was a different
time I had I was born in Edmonton raised
in like housing cooperatives so there
were a lot of kids around a lot of
families and very little parental
supervision so we figured out how to
keep ourselves entertained we were
called in for dark the beginning Epsilon
I was in grade 3 was a very like a fun
chaos well we were still an evangelical
Christian family going to church twice a
Sunday and having that as the coners
cornerstone of our family then my dad
finished his master's degree in library
studies what if we beat a librarian and
he got a job at the left bridge public
library so we moved to left mr. B didn't
move to left which we moved to Raymond
which was a small town populated 90% by
Mormons which was not our religion and
so we didn't really fit in and I had to
hang out with mostly my siblings and my
fantasy what I'll probably got even more
didn't kind of it did get more in-depth
I spent more time in books and less time
with other people we were with other
people they were trying to convert us to
their religion I was probably into my
religion and I went to seven different
elementary schools in grade by grade sex
even though there was only like two big
moves from Edmonton to Raymond from
Raymond to last bridge finally Bodhi you
think a year and a half later so I was
constantly having to make new friends
without really having the capacity to
make new friends I yeah my fantasy life
was probably the key to making them
because when you're a child and you have
access to
fantasy imagination and you can bring
other people into that world at least
when you're pretty young that's a pretty
great trait to have I however they
outgrew it right kids outgrow fantasy
and I never did I like my older sister
outgrew fantasy and so I started playing
with my younger brother and then he
outgrew fantasy and I found friends who
that was their their Miche so my
childhood consisted of moving around a
lot changing friends having God and
Jesus is my central focus and how
important it was that everybody find out
about Jesus so that the second coming of
Christ could happen singing in church on
Sundays reading the Bible I read the
Bible through for the first and only
time when I was in grade four and
cover-to-cover Jesus fantasy and moving
around a lot that was my childhood and
then just the 80s the we watch TV we
thought Nintendo when I was in grade six
so I like childhood childhood didn't
have electronics we didn't have cables
we didn't spend a lot of time on on
television I read a lot of books
especially with my dad being a librarian
and escaped into those fantasy worlds
and created my own I remember having a
field trip where we walked it was
probably like a half an hour to 45
minute walk and telling this story which
I wish I would have recorded I remember
there was like a big white lion maybe
ripped off from Narnia which was a
series my parents read to us like if I
had been a kid in the late 90s I
wouldn't have been allowed to read Harry
Potter but because like witchcraft would
have been very very bad and yet we read
Nardi XRD and was written by a Christian
and then I was allowed to read like
artists I've and and I don't know my
parents were very wishy-washy like we
some years we would practice we would go
trick-or-treating in other years he
wouldn't it kind of depended on which
church we were going into what the
flavor of their Christianity was that
year
and that is my childhood story from like
zero did I mention I recorded this a few
times that I am the middle child of an
older sister and a younger brother which
is also very much you can't not have
that flavor your life your sibling order
is a huge part of who you are your
family dynamics and I very much didn't
want to rock the boat I could see my
older sister and younger brother needing
a lot of attention and so I kind of slid
into the shadows more I had meltdowns a
lot as a young kid and my parents being
young parents really didn't like it so I
shut them down like I shut down my
emotions so I wasn't gonna have that
impact I was a fairly happy kid except
when I had meltdowns so that's my
childhood thank you